// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following best describes virtual commissioning?",
    answer: "Simulating and testing control software and devices before connecting them to the real system",
    options: [
      "Testing control software in a physical environment",
      "Simulating and testing control software and devices before connecting them to the real system",
      "Designing control software for virtual reality systems",
      "Installing virtual machines for industrial automation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the main function for RF:ViPer in virtual commissioning?",
    answer: "Programming function blocks and simulating periphery devices",
    options: [
      "Creating 3D visualizations",
      "Programming virtual machine models",
      "Simulating control software",
      "Programming function blocks and simulating periphery devices"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of a virtual robot controller?",
    answer: "Debugging robot projects virtually",
    options: [
      "Debugging robot projects virtually",
      "Controlling physical robots in real-time",
      "Designing robot hardware components",
      "Simulating virtual reality environments"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is RF::YAMS® used for in virtual commissioning?",
    answer: "Preparing and simulating 3D stations",
    options: [
      "Creating physical prototypes",
      "Simulating 2D environments",
      "Preparing and simulating 3D stations",
      "Testing electrical circuits"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How is RF::ViPer® conneted to the RF::Suite system for virtual commissioning?",
    answer: "Through shared memory",
    options: [
      "Through Wi-Fi connection",
      "Through Bluetooth connection",
      "Through shared memory",
      "Through a physical cable connection"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question:"How are function bLocks created and used in RF::ViPer®?",
    answer: "They are created with periphery element behaviour logic and can be saved in standard libraries for reuse",
    options: [
        "They are imported from CAD software",
        "They are generated automatically",
        "They are predefined templates without customization options",
        "They are created with periphery element behaviour logic and can be saved in standard libraries for reuse"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question:"What type of data does RF::RobSim® support for simulation?",
    answer: "Kinematics data and robot programs",
    options: [
        "CAD models",
        "Kinematics data and robot programs",
        "Electrical schematics",
        "Process flow diagrams"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question:"Which tool is used to create logic and simulate periphery devices in virtual systems during virtual commissining?",
    answer: "RF::ViPer",
    options: [
        "RF::YAMS®",
        "RF::SCOUT®",
        "RF::ViPer",
        "RF::FSBOX®"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:"What types of projects are supported by RF::YAMS®?",
    answer: "Projects developed from Process Simulate, DELMIA, and other 3D tools",
    options: [
        "Projects developed from Process Simulate, DELMIA, and other 3D tools",
        "2D Projects only",
        "Projects developed from CAD software",
        "Projects developed from Microsoft Office Suite"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:"Why is connecting RF::YAMS® with RF::ViPer® significant in virtual commissioing?",
    answer: "It ensures accurate simulation and testing of control systems and periphery components",
    options: [
        "It increases processing speed",
        "It allows for the creation of virtual reality environments",
        "It reduces the cost of software licenses",
        "It ensures accurate simulation and testing of control systems and periphery components"
    ]
  }
  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];